但是这一切都是从我们返回一个函数开始的
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: But it all starts
with us returning a function from
调用，通过运行另一个函数。
the invocation,
from the running of another function.
这是很重要的一部分,
This is a big part,
it's a part that's gonna feel,
好吧我有点明白了。
okay, yeah, I kinda get this.
然而，伙计们，如果我们记下这一点，所有的圈地就会像这样,
And yet, folk, if we get this bit down,
everything enclosure follows like that,
好像很容易似的。
like it's easy.
但是我们必须理解返回一个函数听起来是多么美妙
But we have to understand what sounds
pretty from returning a function
另一个函数。
another function.
是的，我向你保证我已经做过这个演讲了。
And yeah,
I promise you I've given this talk.
我不是评估更多，我在知道这些的插入式公司做这个演讲
I'm not assessing more, I give this talk
at insert companies who knows what this
是我的 be 和本季工程师们。
is my be and this season engineers.
他们真的没有这个小概念。
They really don't have
this little notion down.
在我们做 a 之前，任何真正理解 JavaScript 的东西。
And until we do A,
anything really understand JavaScript.
其次，我们绝对没有能力做个了结，对吧？
And B, we definitely don't have
the ability to get closure, right?
当然，因为我们还没有准备好结束。
Of course,
cuz we don't have closure ready.
所以我们要去理解返回另一个函数的函数,
So we're gonna go and understand
returning a function of another function,
找到了。
here it is.
函数可以从 JavaScript 中的其他函数返回,
Functions can be returned from
other functions in JavaScript,
我们走过去看看。
let's walk through it.
我们从 createFunction 中保存了一个函数,
We've got a function saved
here from createFunction,
我们会给出一个标签 generatedFunc 一个标识符。
we're gonna give a label generatedFunc,
an identifier.
Generatedfunc，我们将为其分配运行 create 函数的输出。
GeneratedFunc, to which we're gonna assign
the output of running create function.
一次运行 create 函数。
One time running create function.
我们怎么知道？
How do we know that?
我看到了 parens，它说去运行这里的代码。
I see parens,
it says go run this code up here.
我们要创建一个执行上下文来运行它,
We're gonna create an execution
context to run it, dive in,
我们要马上保留一个全新的功能。
we're gonna save immediately
a brand new function.
呼叫乘以二。
Call multiplied by two.
我们不会用的,
We're not gonna use it,
我们会直接把它退回到 generatedFunc。
we're instead gonna return it
straight out into generatedFunc.
这样 generatedFunc 将成为一个新的标签
Such that generatedFunc is
gonna be a new label for
这个函数生来就是乘法 by2。
the function that was born as multiplyBy2.
在全局中，局部标号乘以创建函数内部的两个数
In global, the local label multiplied
by two inside of create function's
执行上下文，这将被删除。
execution context,
that's gonna be deleted.
但是它们的函数将在 generatedFunc 中返回
But their functions are gonna be
returned out in the generatedFunc and
我们现在将有一个新的标签为什么是倍增 by2生成的 func。
we'll now gonna have a new label for what
was born as multiplyBy2 generatedFunc.
这有点像另一个翻转，我们正在进入一些东西
It's kinda like the flip of the other
one where we were taking something into
另一个函数，给它一个新的标签。
another function, give it a new label.
现在，我们把它拿出来，给它一个新的标签
Now, we're taking it out,
giving it a new label and
通过那个有 params 的新唱片公司经营。
running it by that new label with params.
那个生成的 func 将会是多倍的 by2。
That generatedFunc is really
gonna be multiplyBy2.
听起来也许不深刻但是民谣我们都知道,
Sounds maybe not profound,
but folk, we get this down,
自然而然就结束了。
closure follows so naturally.
好了我们开始吧。
All right, here we go.
1号线，托德，我们在这儿干什么？
Line 1, Todd, what are we doing here?
托德: 我们正在定义创建函数的函数。
&gt;&gt; Todd: We're defining
the function createFunction.
威尔 · 森特斯: 创造功能，我们把它存在哪里？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: CreateFunction,
and we're storing it where?
托德: 在全局记忆中。
&gt;&gt; Todd: In global memory.
威尔 · 森坦斯: 没错，我们实际上存储了
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: That's right we're
actually storing all the code of
这个函数从来没有忘记这个方块代表所有的代码
the function never lose sight of
this box represents all the code
被定义的函数，被保存到全局内存中。
of the function being defined,
being saved into global memory.
太好了，谢谢托德。
Perfect, thank you to Todd.
现在我们继续下一行？
And now we move on to what line next?
伊森？
Ethan?
伊森: 我们将定义 generatedFunc 的概念。
&gt;&gt; Ethan: We'll be defining
the concepts generatedFunc.
Will Sentance: Beautiful，define the const generatedFunc.
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Beautiful,
define the const generatedFunc.
这就是 generatedFunc，好吗？
There it is generatedFunc, okay?
事情变得有趣了 Ethan 我们卖了那个标签,
Now, things got interesting Ethan,
we sold that label,
标识常量标签产生的 func。
that identify that const
label generatedFunc.
我们要存储分配给它的什么？
What are we're gonna store assign to it?
它的价值是什么？
What's it's value gonna be?
威尔 · 森坦斯: 答案可能只是，我们还不知道。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: The answer
might just be, we don't know yet.
伊森: 我们还不知道。
&gt;&gt; Ethan: We don't know yet.
威尔 · 森特斯: 我们还不知道，它还没有初始化，我们必须去,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: We don't know yet, it's
uninitialized, while we've gotta go and,
你逃不掉的，我们得去做什么，伊森？
you can't get away with that,
we've gotta go and do what, Ethan?
伊森: 调用创建函数。
&gt;&gt; Ethan: Call createFunction.
Will Sentance: 调用 createFunction 和
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Call createFunction and
无论它返回什么，都没有初始化
whatever it returns out, uninitialized for
现在，我们要去关闭和创建功能,
now, we are going to go off and
pull createFunction,
没有争论，没有输入，没有问题。
no arguments, no inputs, no problem.
所有他是一个正常的使一个函数运行。
All he was a normal make a function run.
括号将使函数运行。
Parentheses will make a function run.
这是一个很大的区别。
It's a big distinction.
我们将进入执行环境。
And we're going to enter
that execution context.
我们要创造每个人，因为午餐后表演什么？
We're gonna create everybody
because after lunch shows what?
我们要创造一个全新的？
We're gonna create a brand new?
托德: 执行环境。
&gt;&gt; Todd: Execution context.
威尔 · 森坦斯: 当我们走到这里，不管从这个函数返回什么,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: As we go and here, okay,
whatever is returned out of this function,
可以是数字，可以是字符串，可以是数组
it could be a number, it could be
a string, it could be an array, it could
定义一个函数的代码将被存储到 generatedFunc 中。
be a definition the code of a function
is gonna be stored into generatedFunc.
但是在我们开始之前，布莱登，我们要宣布的是什么,
But before we get to that, Braden, what
is it that we're going to declare, save,
存储在 createFunction 的执行上下文中？
store inside createFunction's
execution context?
我们在那里储存什么？
What are we storing there?
伊森: 你在声明多元 by2函数。
&gt;&gt; Ethan: You're declaring
the multiplyBy2 function.
威尔 · 森特斯: 是的，字面意思是，人们,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah, and
that literally means, people,
这是我们定义的局部临时内存。
this is local temporary memory we define.
没有拼写，对吧？
That's not spelled, right?
定义 multilyby2为，我要做一个不同的颜色，所以
Define multiplyBy2 as,
I'm gonna do a different colors so
我们可以追踪它的旅程，找到 multimyby2。
we can really track its
journey to find multiplyBy2.
这可读吗？
Is that readable?
没关系，把 multilyby2定义为一个函数就是整个代码。
That's okay, define multiplyBy2
as a function is whole code.
凯拉我们现在用的是二乘法吗？
Now, Kayla are we using
multiply by two right now?
我们要调用它，在 createFunctions 执行上下文中调用它吗？
Are we gonna call it, invoke it inside
of createFunctions execution context?
没有 威尔 · 森塔斯: 我们绝对不会,
&gt;&gt; Kayla: No.
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: We absolutely not,
那我们现在怎么办 Kayla？
what are we gonna do instead here, Kayla?
我们要把它归还给常量生成基金会。
&gt;&gt; Kayla: We're gonna return it
to the constant generatedFunc.
威尔 · 森特斯: 太棒了,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Fantastic,
我们要把它返回到恒定的 generatedFunc。
we're gonna return it out into
the constant generatedFunc.
这就是 JavaScript 的作用，它似乎返回了,
Here's what JavaScript does,
it seems returned,
2，它说，i’ ve no i don’t return means,
multiplyBy2, it goes,
I've no I don't return means,
接下来是函数执行上下文的输出。
the next thing is gonna be the output
of this function execution context.
实际上，这将替换对函数的调用
In fact, this is gonna replace
the call to the function and
我们在左手边看到的。
we saw it on the left hand side here.
我知道，但我不知道这个词是什么意思。
I know that but
I have no idea what this word means.
所以它像往常一样发出信号，去寻找记忆。
So it goes off as it always
does to look into memory.
别担心。
Don't worry.
这里有一个函数，它使用这个标签来取值,
There's a function,
it uses that label to take the value,
信不信由你，函数定义是一个值。
which believe it or
not function definition is a value.
函数的代码是一种可以存储的东西，它具有很大的价值
The code of a function is a thing that can
be stored that has a lot of value with
可以用标签存储的东西。
the thing that can be stored with a label.
标识的标签，它的值的花哨名称,
Label for identify,
a fancy name for it value,
这是整个函数的代码。
which is the whole code of the function.
我们在讨论，如果我们接受它，除了标签什么都可以。
We're talking, if we were to take it,
it would be everything but the label.
除了标签之外的所有东西，都是它的主体。
Everything there but the label,
that's the body of it.
Returnnumby2，这就是它的参数 num。
ReturnNumBy2, that's the parameter of it,
num.
所有的存储，这就是这里。
All stored, that's what this is here.
我去拿正如 Kayla 所说我们要把它还回去。
I'm gonna grab, and exactly as Kayla said,
we're gonna return it out.
凯拉，它来了吗，它返回时标签是否带有 multilyby2？
Kayla, does it come, does it get
returned out with its label multiplyBy2?
不，只是定义什么新的全球标签，凯拉？
No, just the definition into
what new global label, Kayla?
通用基金。
&gt;&gt; Kayla: GeneratedFunc.
威尔 · 森特斯: 她说得很对。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Into generatedFunc,
she's spot on.
这就是它，它的正式名称是，只是为了
There it is,
it was formally known as, just for
我们追踪它的目的,
our purposes of keeping track of it,
它以前叫做 multilyby2，但现在不是了，好吗？
it was formerly known as multiplyBy2,
but not anymore, okay?
也就是说，顺便说一下，我甚至可能在这里展示它。
That is also to say by the way,
I might even show it here.
也就是说，我们实际上是在替换函数调用
That is to say that we are literally
replacing that function call and it's
我们要返回到 generatedFunc 中的 multiplyBy2函数定义。
gonna return out that function definition
of multiplyBy2 into generatedFunc.
好的，[声音] ，这很棘手。
Okay, [SOUND], that's tricky.
这个执行环境，各位，它发生了什么？
And this execution context,
everybody, what happens to it?
托德: 消失。
&gt;&gt; Todd: Disappears.
是的，它消失了，被删除了，被关闭了,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah, it disappears,
it's deleted, it's closed,
里面的东西都会被删除。
everything inside of gets deleted.
除了函数返回但是
Well, except the function
got returned that but
除了一些有效的结果，我们确实失去了所有的标签。
we do lose that label everything
besides a bunch of efficient outcomes.
好，现在我们回到 global，我们击中下一行的左手边。
Okay, now we're back into global, where
we hit left hand side of the next line.
上面说要做瑞恩在最后一行左手边的动作。
It says to do what Ryan on the left
hand side of the last line there.
定义一个恒定的结果。
&gt;&gt; Ryan: Define a constant result.
定义一个不变的结果，非常好。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Define
a constant result, very nice.
定义一个恒定的结果。
Okay, define a constant results.
那么这等于什么呢？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: And
so that equal to what?
瑞恩，请讲。
Ryan go ahead.
瑞安: GeneratedFunc。
&gt;&gt; Ryan: GeneratedFunc.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 不完全是,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Not quite,
我甚至不会说精确度在这里是如此重要。
I wouldn't even say that words where
the precision is so important here.
凯拉，你想试试吗？
Kayla do you wanna take a shot?
这是用3调用 generatedfunc 的结果。
&gt;&gt; Kayla: It's the result of
calling generatedfunc with 3.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 是的，那么我们就在这里写吧，她完全正确。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah, so
let's write it here, she's exactly right.
在这里区分函数是非常重要的。
You see it's really important here that
we distinguish between a function.
如果这里没有 parenns，那么结果就是 generatedFunc。
If we just had no parens here,
the result would be generatedFunc.
它只是这个函数的另一个标签。
And it would just be another label for
this function here.
但是相反，这是一个在这里运行这个函数的命令。
But instead, this is a command to go and
run this function here.
所以现在让我们更精确地说明这一点。
So now let's be really precise on this.
Kayla 通用基金会如果你在看这段代码,
Kayla, generatedFunc,
if you're looking at this code here,
人们一直都是这么做的，完全可以理解。
and this what people do all the time,
and totally understandably.
你抬起头，问什么是 generatedFunc？
You look up and
you say what's generatedFunc?
什么是 generatedFunc？
It's the, well, what is generatedFunc?
凯拉，你想试试吗？
Kayla, do you wanna give it a shot?
这就是多倍体的定义。
&gt;&gt; Kayla: It was
the definition of multiplyBy2.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 她说的没错，一般来说，她给了你另一种方式
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: She's spot on, more
generally to give you sort of another way
就创造功能而言。
of putting it, in terms of createFunction.
它和创建函数有什么关系？
What's its relationship to createFunction?
这是跑步的结果。
&gt;&gt; Kayla: It was the result of running it.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 这就是结果。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: It was the result.
这就是结果。
It was the result.
Createfunction 的一次性运行。
The one time running of createFunction.
通用的 func 人员，从那行开始就没有任何关系,
GeneratedFunc people,
has zero relationship from that line on,
从这个倒数第二行在 generatedFunc 有零
from this penultimate line
on generatedFunc has zero
与 createFunction 的关系，它有零连接。
relationship with createFunction,
it has zero connection.
然而，当我们看到这些的时候，我们看到了什么？
And yet
what do we look at that when we see that?
我们就像 generatedFunc 一样运行 createFunction 或者
We're like generatedFunc is kind of
the running of createFunction or
即使是 generatedFunc 也是一种创建函数。
even generatedFunc is
kind of createFunction.
不，所以 JavaScript 是一种同步语言。
No, so
JavaScript is a synchronous language.
做完这一行，继续前进，永远不要再碰它。
Do the line, move on,
never to touch it again.
当你完成了这一行，运行 createFunction,
When you've done that line,
the running of createFunction,
你进去，创建一个新的函数，内部是 multilyby2。
you go in, you create a new function,
multiplyBy2 inside.
它被返回到 generatedFunc 中。
It gets returned out into generatedFunc.
Generatedfunc 是纯粹的、简单的
GeneratedFunc is pure and simply and
只有 create 函数一次运行的结果。
only the result of the one time
running of the create function.
也就是说，它是保存在 generatedFunc 上的，multilyby2的代码。
That is to say that it is saved,
multiplyBy2's code on a generatedFunc.
从这一行开始，它与 createFunction 没有任何关系。
It has nothing to do from that
line on with createFunction.
然而，我们是否倾向于看到这条线？
And yet,
are we prone we see this line here?
当我们看到 generatedFunc 引用时，我们上升并且
When we see generatedFunc refer to,
we go up and
我们发现它与创建函数有关。
we see it's related to createFunction.
我们假设，它与创造函数有某种联系。
We assume, somehow it's got some
relation to createFunction.
它没有任何关系。
It has zero relationship.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 它们之间的联系如此之少，真是不可思议。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: It's quite extraordinary
how little connection it has.
就这一次我知道我一直在纠结但我向你们保证,
It's was a one-time, I know I'm dwelling
on this, but I promise you people,
世界各地的人们都会说，是的，是的，当然,
people around the world are going,
yeah, yeah, sure,
就像是创建函数，是的，明白了。
generatedFunc is like createFunction,
yeah, got it.
我们都有过这样的经历，如果我们得到了这一点，合上你的书，它就是如此
And we've all been there, and if we
get this bit, close your book, it's so
自然地。
naturally.
这实际上是潜在的混乱的原因。
This is actually the cause
of underlying confusion.
所以让我们试着回答更多的问题。
So let's try and answer a few more ways.
当我运行 createFunction 的时候，我进去创建了 multimyby2。
When I ran createFunction at one time I
went inside and I created multiplyBy2.
当我实际执行 createFunction 上下文时，它就被创建了
When I actually did that createFunction
execution context it was created
我不能接触到这里面的任何东西。
by calling it I lose access
to anything inside of here.
除非等等我们问问地图,
Unless, hold on, let's ask map,
我还能在全局中运行 multiplyBy2的函数定义吗？
can I still run the function definition
of multiplyBy2 back in global?
讲者6: 是的 威尔 · 桑特斯: 是啊，怎么会这样？
&gt;&gt; Speaker 6: Yes.
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah, how come?
我可以使用什么? 我可以使用什么标签？
What can I use?
What label can I use?
扬声器6: 你可以使用 generatedFunc。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 6: You can use generatedFunc.
Will Sentance: 我可以使用 generatedFunc，因为 generatedFunc 是
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: I can use generatedFunc,
because generatedFunc is the result of
一次性运行一个 createFunction，结果得到了 multiplyBy2的定义。
one-time running a createFunction, that it
turned out the definition of multiplyBy2.
我还要说多少次？
How many more times do I have to?
接下来我该怎么说？
[LAUGH] Which way should I say it next?
大家听清楚了如果我在运行 generatedFunc,
So to be clear everybody,
if I'm running generatedFunc,
我正在运行这个函数。
I'm running the function that was born as.
讲者6: multilyby2。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 6: MultiplyBy2.
如果我运行 generatedFunc 什么？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: If I'm
running generatedFunc what?
有人说创建，我听到了创建功能这个词。
Someone say created,
I heard the word createFunction.
如果我正在运行 generatedFunc，那么我正在运行的函数是作为什么而诞生的？
If I'm running generatedFunc, I'm running
the function that was born as what?
讲者6: multilyby2。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 6: MultiplyBy2.
威尔 · 森特斯: GeneratedFunc 是代码，最初是什么？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: GeneratedFunc is
the code that was originally what?
讲者6: multilyby2。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 6: MultiplyBy2.
威尔 · 斯坦斯: 没错，就是多倍 by2的定义。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Exactly,
definition of multiplyBy2.
Generatedfunc，它是否与 createFunction 有连接？
GeneratedFunc, does it have
a connection to createFunction?
讲者6: 没有。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 6: No.
不，它是由 createFunction 创建的还是有点像创建的？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: No, did it get created
or sort of get created by createFunction?
是的，但仅此而已，我们继续前进。
Yes, but that was it, and we moved on.
好的如果我在这里运行 generatedFunc 我会创建,
Okay, so, if I'm running generatedFunc
here, I'm gonna create, everybody,
全新的？
a brand new?
演讲者6: 执行情境。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 6: Execution context.
威尔 · 森特斯: 太好了，彼得。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Excellent, Peter.
其他人都是全新的吗？
Everyone else a brand new?
演讲者6: 执行情境。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 6: Execution context.
威尔 · 森特斯: 很好，就是这个。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Very nice, there it is.
好吧，这就是为什么我觉得很困惑的原因。
Okay, and
here's why it's really confusing I think.
让我们进入正题。
Let's go into it.
我们的论点3，占位符是什么？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Our arguments 3,
what's the placeholder?
参数是什么？
What's the parameter?
丹，那是在等那三个吗？
Dan, that's waiting for that 3?
丹: 数字。
&gt;&gt; Dan: Num.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 他说对了，但是这就是为什么人们会加倍困惑的原因。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: He's spot on, but here's
why this is doubly confusing people.
为了找出占位符是什么，丹必须去哪里？
Where did Dan have to go,
to figure out what the placeholder was?
他不得不回到创意公司。
He had to go back into createFunction.
作为一个开发人员，如果你回来了，但是 JavaScript 百分之百没有这样做。
Visually as a developer if you're back in
and yet is JavaScript doing that 100% no.
但是 Dan 不得不回去创造功能，这是多么令人困惑啊
But how damn confusing is that that Dan
had to go back up to create function and
再多看几眼，他就能挽救了？
see more of it and he will saved that?
但这并不是它真正被拯救的地方。
But that's not where it's actually saved.
当我们运行 createFunction 时，这行代码运行了那段代码,
That line there when we ran
createFunction ran that code,
这是创建函数的方式，全局保存在全局内存中。
which was by the way create functions
global saved in global memory.
即使在运行 create 函数时，也没有去备份 create 函数。
Even when it ran create functions
didn't go backups create function.
线程永远不会返回，它不需要返回，因为当它说你创建的时候
The thread never goes back up, it didn't
have to because when it say you create
函数启动时，它将所有代码保存在内存中。
functions that start,
it saved all the code in memory.
它就是从那里抓取代码开始运行的。
That's where it went and
grabbed the code from to start running it.
然后在创建函数 multipleyby2中创建。
And then it created inside of
createFunction multiplyBy2.
它还保存了 multilyby2的代码，包括参数名
And it literally saved the code of
multiplyBy2 including the parameter name
Num，在执行上下文(本地内存)中创建参数 name num。
num, creating parameter name num into
that execution context, local memory.
然后他抓住它，把它放回到全球
And then he grabbed it and
returned it out into global and
存储在 generatedFunc 下。
stored it under generatedFunc.
它进入了我们的记忆
And it's into memory where we go and
获取我们在运行 generatedFunc 时使用的函数代码。
grab the code of that function that
we had when we run generatedFunc.
但问题是，我们看不到这一点，因为我们
But the problem is,
we don't get to see that because we
看不到存储在这里的代码乘以2。
don't get to see visually that code
multiplied by 2 stored over here.
所以我们必须像 Dan 那样，回到上面，但是 JavaScript 没有做到这一点。
So we have to visually as Dan did, go back
up, but JavaScript is not doing that.
它对创建功能没有兴趣。
It has no interest in createFunction.
但是要从视觉上弄清楚如何做到这一点是非常困惑的
But it's pretty doubly confusing
that visually to figure out how
如果 generatedFunc 正在工作，我们必须返回到 createFunction。
the generatedFunc is working,
we have to go back into createFunction.
但只是从我们的角度来看，我们的开发者来看,
But only in terms of our perspective,
our developer looking at it,
不是这样做的。
JavaScript is not doing that.
好的，干得好，丹，没错。
Okay, so well done to Dan, exactly.
现在我们来做数字2，也就是3 × 2，也就是6和
Let's now do number 2,
which is 3 by 2 which is 6 and
我们把它归结为结果。
we return that out into result.
所以它是评价结果转化为结果。
So it's the evaluated result into result.
就是这样。
And there it is.
哇，我们一开始为什么要这么做？
Wow, why did we do all of
this in the first place?
现在我们来讨论一下,
Let's have thumbs over now on
what fundamentally people,
我向你保证这不是我能理解的那种,
I promise you this isn't one of the ones
where you're like I roughly got it,
这是任务的关键部分，所以没关系。
this is the mission-critical
part of closure, so it's okay.
这也不是一件简单的事情。
It's also not like, this is an easy thing.
我向你保证，我已经看到太多有十年经验的开发人员没有
I promise you, I've seen too many
developers with ten years' experience not
在这里真的有执行的精确度，好吗？
really have the precision of
the execution down here, okay?
你把我弄糊涂了，我明白了吗，澄清一下？
You lost me, I'm clear, clarifications?
所有人，大拇指出来，我向你们保证，这是很好的澄清这一点。
Everybody, thumbs out, I promise you,
it's good to have clarifications on this.
威尔 · 森特斯: 好吧，答应我，好吧，答应我，答应我？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Okay, promise,
okay, all right promise, promise?
托德: (笑)威尔 · 森坦斯: 好吧，那么
&gt;&gt; Todd: [LAUGH]
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: All right, so
我要说的是，为什么我保存了一个很好的语义
one thing I will say is this,
why did I save a nicely semantically that
意味着有意义的函数命名在这里，另一个函数,
means kind of meaningfully named
function inside there another function,
然后把它退回去，给它一个很坏的名字，然后在全球范围内使用？
only to then return it out, giving it
a really bad name out and use it globally?
人们只是想在全球范围内找到它。
One will just to find it globally.
我可能已经这样做了。
What I possibly have
done it this way round.
会把人变成。
Is gonna turn out people.
保存一个函数，声明在执行中存储一个函数。
That, saving a function, declaring
storing a function inside the execution.
在本地内存中运行另一个保存函数的上下文
Context of running another functions
of saving inside its local memory
在另一个函数中。
inside another function.
当该函数返回时，它将获得最强大的
When that function gets returned out,
it gets the most powerful
我们可以要求 JavaScript 的属性加值特性。
property bonus feature of
JavaScript that we can ask for.